<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PhoneParLoan</string>
    <string name="bundle">bundle</string>
    <string name="agreement">By signing this agreement I promise to pay this and that and I agree this amount to be debited from the bank account that is associated with the debit card I will be providing sort of thing</string>
    <string name="user_id">user_id</string>
    <string name="otp">otp</string>
    <string name="demo_otp">demo_otp</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="mobile">mobile</string>
    <string name="id">id</string>
    <!--<string name="finkey">u4JBn55Pus7oyWkD7nhao541Yk6Maevf3zLLLENW</string>-->
    <string name="finkey">eiEqFpWrN5393m8eR4vtT8AA9ePndE8E7erV7dKm</string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_the_privacy_policy">I agree to the <u>privacy policy</u></string>
    <string name="i_agree_new_term_condition">* we will share your loan requirements, loan application and relevant details with our loan fulfillment partners, read <u>Privacy Policy</u></string>
    <string name="otp_text">We have sent you an otp via sms \n for mobile number verification </string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_the_terms_and_conditions">I agree to the <u>terms and conditions</u></string>
    <string name="internet_error">Please check your internet connection try again!</string>
    <string name="kys_help_desc">Know Your Customer (KYC) os a process that has to be complied by financial institutions, where by these set of institutions obtain information about the identity and address of the customers.</string>
    <string name="kys_help_desc_additional">You may upload docs like - Loan closure letter or mail or screenshots if any; office ID card/ business card; ongoing loan schedule if any.</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="update">update</string>
    <string name="error_in_posting_data">Something went wrong!</string>
    <string name="error_in_validating_pan_card">Not able to verify your PAN Card. Please check your PAN again.</string>
    <string name="error_in_saving_sms">Not able to verify your Salary Proof. Please check your SMS again.</string>
    <string name="error_in_validating_bank_account">Not able to verify your Bank account number and IFSC code. Please check again.</string>
    <string name="salary_slip_sms_number">09818464646</string>
    <string name="rating_experience_text">Awesome \n\n Please rate your experience</string>
    <string name="do_you_want_to_change_mobile_number">Are you sure you want to change your mobile number</string>
    <string name="copy_salary_message_from_your_bank_text_in_your_messaging_app_and_click">Copy salary message (in English) from your bank text in your messaging app and click \"PASTE\" button below</string>
    <string name="we_need_to_verify_your_salary">We need to verify your salary</string>
    <string name="regex_amount_string">/[rR][sS]\.?\s[,\d]+\.?\d{0,2}|[rR][sS]\.?[,\d]+\.?\d{0,2}|[iI][nN][rR]\.?\s*[,\d]+\.?\d{0,2}|[aA][mM][tT]\:?\-?\s*[,\d]+\:?\-?\d{0,2}/s</string>
    <string name="please_check_all_permissions">Please grant all permissions to proceed further.</string>
    <string name="copy_salary_message">Copy salary message</string>
    <string name="copy_message_additional_text">\nNavigate to your messaging app and copy the message from your bank notifiying about month\'s salary. \n\n Example message: \n\nAmount of Rs 58,000 has been credited to your account by Organic Water Supply Pvt Ltd. Available balance is Rs. 70,000 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_salary_verification_fail">SalaryVerificationFailActivity</string>
    <string name="in_order_to_get_a_loan_we_need_to_evaluate_your_using_digital_underwriting">In order to get a loan we need to evaluate you using digital underwriting</string>
    <string name="register_back_Kill"> Are you sure you want to exit ?</string>
    <string name="success_android_side_underwriting_failed_on_loan_app_count">You have successfully cleared the salary verification process.\nHowever you do not pass the other verification criteria.\n You can reapply after 15 days.\n\n For more clarification contact us at <u>info@phoneparloan.com</u></string>
    <string name="you_have_not_cleared_salary_verification_process">You have not cleared the salary verification process through our underwriting process.Please provide valid salary sms.\nFor more clarification contact us at <u>info@phoneparloan.com</u></string>
    <string name="under_maintenance">Under Maintenance </string>
    <string name="update_application_title">New Update available </string>
    <string name="update_application_message">Please update your application to latest version </string>
    <string name="rejectionMessage">We regret to inform you that your loan request has been declineWhat is PhoneParLoan?d. This is because you do not meet one or more of our eligibility criteria</string>
    <string name="refer">Simple solution to daily cash crunch needs - PhoneParLoan.\n<u> https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.phoneparloanin</u></string>
    <string name="q1"> What is PhoneParLoan?</string>
    <string name="a1">PhoneParLoan is the fastest credit line based instant loan app in partnership with leading NBFCs. We give instant personal loan online with zero collateral and interest rates as low as 2% for 7 to 30 days duration.</string>
    <string name="q2">What is the 1 Rupee transaction for? Is it the processing fees?</string>
    <string name="a2">No. 1 rupee transaction is NOT a processing fee and is fully refundable. A nominal amount of Rs. 1 is charged for the combined purpose of verification and enabling transaction for the User.</string>
    <string name="q3">What is the amount and duration of loan you provide?</string>
    <string name="a3">PhoneParLoan provides a personal loan starting ₹ 2000 to ₹ 20,000 online for a duration of 7 days/ 15 days/ 30 days.</string>
    <string name="q4">What are the fees and interest charges I have to pay? Are there hidden fees?</string>
    <string name="a4">At PhoneParLoan, we pride ourselves in being customer friendly and transparent. While applying for the loan, the interest rates and fee structure will be visible to you. So you are absolutely clear on what you are paying for. Here is what you pay, no hidden fees: -- An Interest Rate of 2% -- A Processing Fee of 7%. The exact interest rate varies depending on the tenure of the loan.</string>
    <string name="q5">What happens if I miss the payment on the due date?</string>
    <string name="a5">We will be reminding you on your app to pay on or before the due date. Most people do not realize this but missing your payment on the due date will have the following negative effects: a) In the event of your failure to make full payment of the total amount due on the repayment Date, Phoneparloan shall charge an interest of three percent (3%) on the remaining amount of credit. b) Phoneparloan shall suspend your use of its Services. c) Our partner bank will report this to the credit bureaus (CIBIL, Experian, Equifax, Highmark) and your credit history will be negatively impacted. You will feel the impact in the future, when you try to take any other loan or credit card (e.g. a Home loan or a Car/Two-wheeler loan). d) If you don’t pay after continual reminders, the bank might initiate recovery proceedings. So, please don’t miss your payments!</string>
    <string name="q6">How much time do you take to approve the loan? </string>
    <string name="a6">It would take 1 working days to process your loan.</string>
    <string name="q7">Can I take the money in cash?</string>
    <string name="a7">The money is transferred directly to your bank account and you can use your regular ATM card to withdraw funds and use them as you wish. The funds are yours.</string>
    <string name="q8">What happens if I don’t pay back the loan?</string>
    <string name="a8">The Reserve Bank of India has nominated 4 credit agencies (e.g. CIBIL) that track your financial credit scores. If you do not repay or delay your repayment, our partner bank will automatically report it to these agencies, which will record the information. This can lower your credit score. Once your credit score is affected, you will not only lose PhoneParLoan access, but all your future loan applications will be negatively impacted. You might not be able to get loans easily to buy a house, a car or a two-wheeler or get a credit-card, as all the lending institutions in the country check with these agencies before approving your loan. The bank might also initiate legal recourse to recover the money from you. In short, please do not use the funds if you don’t think you cannot repay the loan.</string>
    <string name="q9">What is the reason of my loan rejection?</string>
    <string name="a9">In order to grant loans, we have set certain parameters and criteria basis which we reject/approve the loan. Even if you successfully clear the salary verification process, there is a chance that you might not pass the other verification criteria and hence won’t be eligible for a loan. However, you can try again after 15 days with a clear and complete set of information that meets all our criteria, for a successful loan approval.</string>
    <string name="q10">You ask for Debit card details for 1 Rs. payment. How safe is it?</string>
    <string name="a10"> This is a very legitimate concern. However, you need not worry. We cannot access or tamper your financial details as we establish a read-only connection with your bank and ATM card security is not breached. Your bank details are stored securely. </string>
    <string name="q11">Whom should I connect for other queries?</string>
    <string name="a11">For any clarification or grievances, you may contact us on _____________ and you can also drop us a mail at info@phoneparloan.com. All our customer service executives are available from 11 a.m till 4 p.m from Monday to Saturday.</string>
    <string name="q12">What type of phones do you support?</string>
    <string name="a12">We currently support Android phones only.</string>
    <string name="q13">What if I get stuck and my app shuts down before the completion of the application on the app? Do I have to restart the process?</string>
    <string name="a13">No, you just need to open our app and you can continue from where you left. In case of any other problems feel free to contact us at info@phoneparloan.com</string>
    <string name="q14">What security measures do you employ?</string>
    <string name="a14">We use SSL and other industry standard encryption technologies while exchanging sensitive data with the application and with banking partners. Our systems have been designed such that most of the steps are automated. Our IT systems are checked and approved by the IT and Data Security teams of our partner banks. We are legally compliant with all data privacy and IT security norms in India.</string>
    <string name="permission">PERMISSIONS</string>
    <string name="permission_subtext">Giving permissions helps in giving out the\nbest offer for you</string>


    <string name="SmsPermission">SMS</string>
    <string name="AppsPermission">APPS</string>
    <string name="PhonePermission">PHONE</string>
    <string name="ContactsPermission">CONTACTS</string>
    <string name="StoragePermission">STORAGE</string>
    <string name="LocationPermission">LOCATION</string>
    <string name="AccountsPermission">ACCOUNTS</string>
    <string name="CameraPermission">CAMERA</string>
    <string name="SMSPermissionDescription">Collect and monitor only financial transactional SMS for description of the transactions and corresponding amounts for credit risk assessment.Other SMS Data will not be accessed</string>
    <string name="APPSPermissionDescription">Collect and monitor list of installed apps in your device for credit profile enrichment</string>
    <string name="PhonePermissionDescription">Collect and monitor specific information about your device including your hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identities like IMEI and serial number, user profile information, wi-fi information, and mobile networks information to uniquely identify the devices are not able to act on your behalf to prevent frauds</string>
    <string name="ContactsPermissionDescription">Collect contacts information to automatically detect references information for your customized credit scoring</string>
    <string name="StoragePermissionDescription">We need to upload your identity documents from storage for the loan application in the app</string>
    <string name="LocationPermissionDescription">Collect and monitor information about the location of your device to do risk assessment for credit scoring</string>
    <string name="AccountsPermissionDescription">Collect and monitor list of accounts in your device for credit profile enrichment</string>
    <string name="CameraPermissionDescription">We need to upload your identity supporting documents through camera</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText"><u>Read our privacy policy in detail by clicking on this link </u> </string>
    <string name="poweredbyfinbox"><u>Powered by FinBox</u> </string>
    <string name="enter_your_statement_password">Enter password (if applicable)</string>
    <string name="select_applicable_option">Select what is applicable</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="salary_copy_desc">Navigate to the messaging app and copy the message from your bank notifying about month\'s salary.</string>
    <string name="salary_paste_desc">Paste the salary SMS and get your\n salary verified</string>
    <string name="min_loan_amount">\u20B9 10,000</string>
    <string name="max_loan_amount">\u20B9 1,50,000</string>
    <string name="existing_emi_text">Enter monthly EMI Eg: \u20B9 2500/- </string>
    <string name="loan_partner_text">You are eligible to apply for loan of \u20B9 </string>
    <string name="bringing_it_up_in_a_moment">Bringing it up in a moment...</string>
    <string name="loan_application">Registration</string>
    <string name="please_wait_loading_view">Loading... Please Wait</string>
    <string name="your_application_has_been_forwarded_to_our_loan_partner">\u2022 Your application has already been forwarded to our Loan Partner</string>
    <string name="min_reruired_salary_text">Minimum Requirement is ₹20000</string>
    <string name="valid_address">Valid Indian Passport, Voter ID card, Valid Driving License, Aadhaar card, Utility Bill</string>
    <string name="review_appplication_text">Your application is under review and \n you will be notified soon</string>
    <string name="prod_key_cv">TXk7odHv6uYsMAPMWiRX8v8bzreQqzmz</string>
    <string name="uat_key_cv">EzUhHr4OU0TAUGqUslFFjb7nLD21YAw5</string>
    <string name="ppl_authorization_token">Bearer h2P9IWHOL6r7R85kku0VkBxL4HaH7m7PQmlhKtuNS0iXD3GsSow7EJk97if2YdqHPCHYjBLEElSPrSNV</string>
    <string name="txt_help">Help</string>
    <string name="txt_need_any_help">Need any help?</string>
    <string name="txt_reach_out">You can always reach out to us</string>
    <string name="txt_email_phone_par_loan">info@phoneparloan.com</string>
    <string name="txt_click_to_drop_mail">Click to drop an email</string>
    <string name="txt_mobile_phone_par_loan">9818464646</string>
    <string name="txt_click_to_call">Click here to call</string>
    <string name="pending_text"> Get in touch with our loan officers \n Monday - Saturday (10:00 am -6:30 pm )</string>
    <string name="txt_webview_loader"> While we redirect your loan application and relevant details with our loan fulfillment partners. \n \n Your data is secured with us and not shared outside of our partnership network.</string>
    <string name="txt_consent_nbfc"> Please allow us to share your loan requirements with our 7 NBFC partners.</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">prefsPPL</string>
    <string name="saved_app_data_for_cv">appDataSavedByCV</string>
    <string name="reference_1">Reference 1</string>
    <string name="provide_hr_admin_information">Provide HR/Admin information</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went wrong...</string>
    <string name="changed_your_mind">Changed your mind?</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try AGAIN</string>
    <string name="rs_49_566_00_is_credited_to_your_a_c_xxxx8627_on_02_may_19_on_account_of_marriott_salary_april_19">Rs. 49,566.00 is credited to your A/c XXXX8627 on 02-MAY-19 on account of Marriott Salary April 19</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="reference_2">Reference 2</string>
    <string name="provide_colleague_information">Provide Colleague information</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="_20">20%</string>
    <string name="your_job">Your job</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="analysing_data">Analysing Data...</string>
    <string name="trying_to_get_a_loan_decision_in_few_seconds">Trying to get a loan decision in few seconds.</string>
    <string name="changed_your_mind">Changed your mind?</string>
    <string name="start_again">START AGAIN</string>
    <string name="thank_you_for_choosing_phone_par_loan">Thank You for choosing Phone Par Loan</string>
    <string name="what_s_next">What\'s next?</string>
    <string name="apply_for_a_new_loan">Apply for a new loan</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_phoneparloan">Welcome to PhoneParLoan</string>
    <string name="instant_loan_upto_5_000">Instant loan upto ₹5,000</string>
    <string name="digital_kyc_s">Digital KYC\'s</string>
    <string name="fill_in_loan_application_in_less_than_15_minutes">Fill in loan application in less than 15 minutes</string>
    <string name="sorry">Sorry!</string>
    <string name="we_can_not_take_your_application_forward_as_you_do_not_get_your_salary_in_a_bank_account">We can not take your application forward as you do not get your salary in a bank account.</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="personal_details">Personal Details</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="select_your_gender">Select your gender</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="personal_email_id">Personal Email ID</string>
    <string name="dob_as_per_id_proof">DOB (as per ID proof)</string>
    <string name="pan_card">PAN Card</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="proceed">PROCEED</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_card">Add a new card</string>
    <string name="loan_re_payment_amount">Loan re-payment amount</string>
    <string name="_500">500</string>
    <string name="debit_card_details">Debit card details</string>
    <string name="enable_one_click_checkout">Enable one click checkout</string>
    <string name="pay_now">Pay now</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="country_name">Country Name</string>
    <string name="code">Code</string>
    <string name="not_eligible">Not eligible</string>
    <string name="we_will_need_digital_copies_of_your_original_kyc_s_so_please_keep_the_following_ready">We will need digital copies of your Original KYC\'s so please keep the following ready.</string>
    <string name="email_id">Email ID</string>
    <string name="designation_position">Designation/Position</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="email_id">Email ID</string>
    <string name="designation_position">Designation/Position</string>
    <string name="name_on_pan_card">Name on PAN Card</string>
    <string name="name_gmail_com">name@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth_dd_mm_yyyy">Date of birth (dd/mm/yyyy)</string>
    <string name="pan_number_eisxxx956x">PAN number (EISXXX956X)</string>
    <string name="flat_house_no_floor_building">Flat/House no./Floor/Building</string>
    <string name="pin_code">Pin Code</string>
    <string name="debit_card_number">Debit card number</string>
    <string name="expiry">Expiry</string>
    <string name="cvv">CVV</string>
    <string name="name_on_card">Name on card</string>
    <string name="please_tell_us_the_reason_for_taking_this_loan">Please tell us the reason for taking this loan</string>
    <string name="debit_card_number">Debit card number</string>
    <string name="expiry">Expiry</string>
    <string name="cvv">CVV</string>
    <string name="name_on_card">Name on card</string>
    <string name="bank_account_number">Bank account number</string>
    <string name="re_enter_bank_account_number">Re-enter Bank account number</string>
    <string name="ifsc_code">IFSC code</string>
    <string name="select_bank">Select Bank</string>
    <string name="select_branch">Select Branch</string>
    <string name="full_name_as_in_pan_card">Full Name (As in PAN Card)</string>
    <string name="surname">Surname</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth_dd_mm_yyyy">Date of birth (dd/mm/yyyy)</string>
    <string name="pan_card_number">PAN card number</string>
    <string name="monthly_income_rs">Monthly Income (Rs.)</string>
    <string name="company_name">Company name</string>
    <string name="brand_name">Brand Name</string>
    <string name="company_email">Company Email</string>
    <string name="linkedin_link_https_www_linkedin_com_profile_id">LinkedIn Link(https://www.linkedin.com/profile_id)</string>
    <string name="address_line_1">Address line 1</string>
    <string name="address_line_2">Address line 2</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="state_ut">State / UT</string>
    <string name="pin">PIN</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="enter_your_monthly_salary">Enter your monthly salary</string>
    <string name="enter_company_name">Enter company name</string>
    <string name="what_you_do">What you do</string>
    <string name="enter_work_email_id">Enter Work Email ID</string>
    <string name="enter_reason_for_taking_this_loan">Enter reason for taking this loan</string>
    <string name="address_line_1">Address line 1</string>
    <string name="address_line_2">Address line 2</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="state_ut">State / UT</string>
    <string name="pin">PIN</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="address_line_1">Address line 1</string>
    <string name="address_line_2">Address line 2</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="state_ut">State / UT</string>
    <string name="pin">PIN</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="enter_pdf_password">Enter pdf password</string>

</resources>


